アドキュア
just that it's cold today it reminds me it's almost New Year's so almost mm-hmm
yeah it's close um it's still November though hey there he is ah morning it's
real chilly today ain't it he's in his blazer why do you sound so excited about
refreshing I haven't seen it since spring but you noticed huh this mess oh your
hair so that wasn't it oh man then I should have told you my bedhead was just
a new hairstyle hey come here I got something awesome to show you awesome
okay see you around he said it was his bedhead how cute it's the new ogre a
flavor the juice box version of Hayakuni issue because a high is surrounded by
everyone like this I love how happy he seems oh yeah I used to think it's
incredible how they gather around him I want to be more like that one day
just as the seasons change over time little by little my feelings start to as
well oh my gosh this is getting so annoying your boyfriend yep that same
college student yeah every single day and every single night he's like what are you
doing who are you with let's meet up right now why don't you reply right away but
why can't you come out are you with a guy like wake up in the morning then I go to
school after that I'm in class with my friends all day and at night I'm just
sleeping yeah that is true but seriously Yano Jean why are you dating a guy like
that he asked I wonder why guys are like this they act mature and grown up but
then they show their true colors I used to think it was such a pain in the butt to
hang out girls that they were catty but guys are so much worse oh is that how it
is no this is just a really problematic example you'd have to love someone a lot
to be that invested seems romantic relationships come in all sorts of
farms oh Rio I'm coming over tonight so be home sure let me keep playing that one
game from where I left off okay but or how about a fighting game definitely not
when she's when Sanada are together their energies really match each other my
eyes are only for Chizuru yes I can't think of two people who'd be better
together a perfect pair but I wonder how she feels if I had to guess I think she
probably like some back
oh pops hi there yo sup Chizu oh it's cold oh I'll help during winter break again
okay uh we appreciate it good to have our poster girl around yeah I guess it
is isn't it I'm gonna head upstairs now sure but I mean it when I say it Chizu I
really do wish you were our daughter
if it were my choice you know I would be
hmm already going to bed you took too long what the hell I told you I was coming
damn it I died stupid lion chimera you mean that reminds me of you talking in your sleep
huh I have never once talked in my sleep oh thing how dare the dumb lion chimera
so by the way is um there anything on your wish list real
hmm under 500 yen a new baseball glove 500 yen not shoulder massage tickets
I'd be okay with anything so thank you I never actually said I'm getting you something
sure thanks anyway I'm leaving okay
oh I meant to ask on New Year's
actually never mind it's nothing good night
I see that's what you wanted to talk about
hello yeah dad's taking a bath right now sure wait next week
I gotta tell her soon huh
hey shop with me today shopping oh no I can't huh why because I'm meeting my boyfriend and I need to see
him as soon as possible bye I'm so free
seriously awesome what are you buying oh I'm getting for you a present for his birthday it's coming up soon
yes that's great well you know I'm like a crazy loyal friend so let me go
get it to chill Joe you don't understand she's always looking at me with this passionate gaze you're the one who's looking at her like that you probably don't even know
know her name do you know her name do you know her name do you do you happen to believe in destiny listen can't you hear it drawing near the deafening sound
you know her name do you know her name do you know her name do you know her name do you know what did you give him last year
what did you give him last year shoulder massage tickets because I was broke
shoulder massage tickets he chose to use them all up right there on the spot
massaged his shoulders for three full hours wow she must really care about Sonata's physical health huh this year I've got a 500 yen budget
it's perfect a new baseball glove is out of the question but maybe a glove bag hold this for a sec
yes what now I do have enough sweet then I guess I'll be extra generous this year
love
that was the perfect purchase I'm really happy for you Jisoo
a mini skirt oh well I thought it might be a good idea to change up my style once in a while
ramen ramen ramen ramen ramen I want to ask I wonder if it's okay to or is it bad
but if I go with my gut right now seems like a good time
um Jisoo I I was wondering if you have a crush on someone
huh
I did it
what the heck that's so random I do
it's always been a one-sided thing though
always
yeah I've had this little crush for a super long time wait then does that mean
we've been friends since childhood
the problem is he really just thinks of me as a little sister that's not true huh say what it's a punch it's fine really I'm okay with it I'm a kid after all there's no way I'm even on his radar I totally understand
that's why I've decided I'm gonna become a real catch once I grow up you never know right
I'm glad I ended up asking her
I've never seen Jisoo with an expression like this before
but still I don't get to see him much these days I miss him huh he lives way up in Sapporo so there's not much I can do about that
oh
he didn't come back for last Obone either which means it's been almost a year now
but I know for sure he'll be coming back for New Year's
he better watch out cuz I'm a full-blown high school girl now
wait
uh what
I'm getting kinda confused so
is it okay if I ask this straight out
what's up
so the person you've been talking about
you mean Sanada right Jisoo
uh
Sawako
wait did you think I was talking about Ryu
uh
you've got it all wrong
hmm we've grown up together so he's more like a brother than anything else
though I wouldn't mind if we actually became siblings
you think of him as a brother
see the person I like is his older brother
oh man makes me blush
um
huh
does Sanada know all of that
real
there's no way he wouldn't know
so this whole time he already knew
why
uh
no reason
really it's nothing
second
can't hear you Sanada
right
you guys too
again
you hadn't gone home yet
well the gang and I were trying to cheer Joe up
as reckless as usual I see
but yeah we decided we're gonna throw him a party to help him get back on his feet
care to join us
we're thinking next weekend
next weekend
oh
that doesn't really work for me
you got plans
not exactly
but
that's when
my brother's back home
what about something like this
looks cold
you'd really have to brace yourself
I'd be shivering
that's no problem
because I'm all fired up
plus
Jesus glowing right now
would have made it in love
I get it
seeing the person you like
can make you so incredibly happy
oh hey Ryu
morning
hi
good morning
morning
hey what's up
hi good morning
Kasehaya
what do you think about these
what's that
winter stuff
yep
a mini skirt
huh
how much do those go for
um
looks like 15,000
yeah
I forgot I was dead broke right now
I really wanted to have it for New Year's
oh New Year's
you want to get some cash then right
no that's too late
I don't know how long Toru's staying
it may just be New Year's Eve or dead
I uh
so his name is Toru huh
I didn't say anything just now
I didn't right
uh
yeah I guess not
what's with all the drama you guys
oh
Yanochi
we broke up
so we dumped you
no I dumped him
and it was a total nightmare
yeah
can definitely see that
I was honest about how I felt
and gently suggested breaking up
and he
I'm sorry
I didn't mean to
you're the only thing I have left
let's move in together
okay
please
this is pointless
the guy isn't listening to a single word
coming out of my mouth
but yeah I didn't really like him
he was just totally annoying
wow sorry I assumed you were into him
after all my complaining that was your takeaway
I want to comfort her but I can't think of the right words to say
I know that it wasn't meant to be
but at the same time it's not any fun when things have to end like this either
poor thing
huh
what's going on with you
why are you acting like I was the one who got dumped
there's someone else who got dumped here
comrades in heartbreak
don't lump me in with you
any kind of romance involves some sort of heartbreak
but it's still tough each time
like I said
I'm the one who did the breaking up
not him
hide your pain from me
come on let's talk about it together
you can't be honest or are you Iyano?
Ryu
you haven't told Yoshida yet
have you?
well it isn't easy to bring it up
do you think you'd tell her?
or
would I?
I think I would
and the rest
that's on her
that's not my call
I figured you might say that Shota
huh
well
you're probably right though
because if Chizuru doesn't know
and we end up running into my brother
it's gonna be a real problem
but still
it's hard
new year's?
a mini skirt?
sounds great to me
really?
good
I'm thinking about getting a frilly one
get one that looks good on you
you think it'd look bad?
this is real girl talk
I'm so curious
I wonder what kind of guy he is
hey
can we go see him too?
what?
no
I think I'd die
Jesus seems so happy
oh no
I'm getting all excited about myself
even though our Yano is suffering
I'm fine
you really don't have to worry about it
I'm so sorry Yano
you have to cheer up
hey
why don't we throw an awesome party
to help get your spirits up
we can use my house
uh yeah sure
then let's have a sleepover on friday
you too Sawago
sleepover?
I can come too?
we're all gonna play a fighting game together
oh a game?
Chizuru
it's me
hmm?
I'm coming in
hey
don't just barge in here
without permission
I could have been changing clothes or something
yeah yeah
and I could say the exact same thing to you
what's up?
it's a rare treat for you to come visit me
here
hmm
you don't want any?
we should talk
close one
what's wrong?
it's nothing
Chizuru
here's the thing
no go home
just leave
get out of here
no
but I need to talk
go
what am I supposed to do?
up until now
just interacting with others
was enough to overwhelm me
because that alone
was so difficult
I never even thought about romance
but I'm sure that romantic relationships
must be just as difficult as friendship
the reason I can understand that
at least a little
is probably because of how certain I am
that I've fallen in love with Kasehaya
okay
In the sky, it won't come to the sky
It won't come to the sky
I want to know that I want to know
It's not that I want to know
It's not that I want to see
I want to see the sky
The sky is filled with light
It's not that I want to see the sky
I want to see the sky
Just see it
In the sky because light
The sky is solid
You can use the sky
The sky isう
It's not that I can't go to the sky
But you can go to the sky
The sky is so toxic
You can take it
It's not that I can love it
You can take the snow
You have three Mum
You